businesscatalyst.com 2012-04-13

# Adobe Business Catalyst - Privacy Policy

Adobe is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to enable individuals and organizations to establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through Adobe Sites that have been certified by TRUSTe, including this site, [www.businesscatalyst.com](http://www.businesscatalyst.com/). The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from this Site or any of the Products and Services. TRUSTe has not certified any of the disclosures in this Privacy Policy that relate to the Products and Services.

Business Catalyst respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information that you provide to us. This statement explains our policies and practices regarding the use and disclosure of your personal information by Business Catalyst. Please note that, Business Catalyst reviews and updates this Privacy Policy from time to time as needed without notice. Therefore, you should review the terms of this policy periodically to make sure that you are aware of how Business Catalyst collects and uses personal information. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Business Catalyst as explained below.

* ## Personal Information.

You have complete control over your personal information. In general, you can visit our web site without providing us with any personal information. However, there are instances where we must have your personal information in order for us to grant you an access to our protected and secured sites. This information may include registration data (your name, address, email address, phone number, title, etc.), information request data and response data ("User Information"). When you receive your confirmation email or when you receive any email from the list server, you will be given instructions on how to remove yourself from the list.

* ## Use of User Information.

We intend to use such information for purposes of supporting your and your employers relationship with Business Catalyst by designing a web site content that is suitable to your needs and alerting you to new product and service offerings as they become available. This User Information may be retained by Business Catalyst to verify compliance with the agreement between Business Catalyst and your employer, to keep track of the domains from which people visit us, to create a user profile to better serve you and your employer, or to simply contact you either electronically or otherwise. If you decide that we should not use your personal User Information to contact you, please let us know and we will not use that information for such purpose. However, please do not submit any User Information if you are less than 18 years of age.

* ## Disclosure of User Information.

Business Catalyst does not sell, trade or transfer User Information to third parties. However, we may share User Information with our business partners for marketing, advertising or product/service offering purposes. For example, we provide User Information to our service providers for direct emailing of our newsletters, online surveys or notifications on Business Catalyst Offerings to our viewers. We also disclose User Information if: we have your consent; we need to share it in order to provide you with the products and/or services you requested; we respond to a court order or you violate our Terms of Use. You may separately agree to provide your personal information to third parties that provide content for Business Catalyst Offerings, in order to access and/or use their products and/or services. If you agree to provide such information to these third parties, then your personal information will be subject to their privacy policies.

* ## Accuracy and Security.

The accuracy and security of the User Information is important to Business Catalyst. Currently, you may review and request updates to your User Information retained by contacting Business Catalyst. If you contact us to correct your User Information, we will attempt to correct such inaccuracies in a timely manner. Business Catalyst is concerned with the security of your User Information and is committed to taking reasonable steps to protect it from unauthorized access and use of that personal information. To that end, we put in place the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial policies and procedures to secure your personal User Information. We also continue to implement procedures to maintain accurate, complete and current User Information.

* ## Usernames and Passwords.

Access to certain content on our web site may be allowed under a written agreement between you or your employer and Business Catalyst and will require a username and/or password. In some cases, failure to provide personal information may prevent you from accessing certain Business Catalyst web site(s) containing certain confidential information, products, services, or promotional offers ("Business Catalyst Offerings"). By accessing and using our protected and secured web site(s), you agree to maintain the confidentiality of the username and password you selected to access such site(s) and consent to our Terms of Use.

* ## Tracking, use of cookies, web beacons and similar devices.

In order to improve our Products and Services and the Site and provide more convenient, relevant experiences to our customers, we and our vendors and agents may use "cookies," "web beacons," and similar devices to track your activities. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card and enables Adobe to record your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. A web beacon is a small transparent gif image that is embedded in an HTML page or email used to track when the page or email has been viewed. A similar device may be used by which a Product and Service may send data to a server when a set of user-initiated events occur such as the "Add to Cart" button is clicked. This device is similar to a cookie in that it tracks your visit and the data can only be read by the server that receives the data. It is different than a cookie in that it is not browser-based, may not function as an identification card, and does not store any data on your computer.

While Adobe uses cookies and similar devices to track your use of the Site and the Products and Services (such as the number of downloads, types of Products and Services used and downloaded, how many users we receive daily, the Site pages visited), and web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, Adobe does not generally use this information to identify you personally. Exceptions to this are noted in this Privacy Policy. If you expressly provide consent for the Site or the Product and Service to "remember" the unique identifier that you select when you register for various activities on the Site or the Products and Services, that unique identifier will be stored on a persistent cookie on your computer and that unique identifier will be linked to your Registration Information. As a result, your navigation path around the Site and the Products and Services will be tracked in identifiable form.

Adobe may also collect data about your online activities on the Sites for use in providing content and advertising tailored to your interests; if this occurs, you will be able to [choose whether or not to have your information collected for such purpose](http://businesscatalyst.com/Misc/optout.html). Some Products and Services allow the tracking of access to or use of Products and Services by users, as opposed to Adobe. For example, certain Products and Services allow document authors to restrict access to documents, track access to or use of those documents, or involve communications and transmission of data over the Internet to verify the authenticity of documents, authors and recipients. In many cases, this type of tracking will be obvious to you as a user of the Products and Services, and in others, the software and services license or terms of use, pop-up boxes, or email messages will inform you of these features and your options, such as disabling options.

* ## External Links.

Business Catalyst web site provides links to other third party web sites. Even if the third party is affiliated with Business Catalyst through a business partnership or otherwise, Business Catalyst is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links. These links are provided to you for convenience purposes only and you access them at your own risk.

* ## Terms of Use.

Please also see our Terms of Use, which describes the restrictions, disclaimers, indemnification and limitation of liability governing the use of the entire Business Catalyst web site.

* ## Privacy Complaints.

Adobe takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that Adobe has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write to the Adobe Privacy Officer at the following address or fill out a [privacy complaint form](http://www.adobe.com/misc/privacy_inquiry.html).

Adobe Systems Incorporated   
Privacy Officer/Customer Information   
Legal Department, A17   
345 Park Avenue   
San Jose, CA 95110-2704   
USA

Email: [privacy-officer@adobe.com](mailto:privacy-officer@adobe.com). 

In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your complaint or your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the [TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process](https://www.truste.org/pvr.php?page=complaint), by mail at WatchDog Complaints, TRUSTe, 55 Market Street, 2nd Floor, San Francisco, CA, USA 94105, by phone at +1 415-520-3400, or by fax at +1 415-520-3420. If you are mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of the company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution process, see <http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint> or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English.

TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with this Site to resolve your concerns.
